Once the adapter is initialized, let's bind it to the list view. But
you may notice that we don't have a reference to the list view in our fragment.
It was only defined in the layout XML. The system takes and
inflates layout XML files. And
turns them into a full view hierarchy with a root layout of the main activity at
the very top of the view tree. We can also assign IDs to each view in the tree,
but it's not required if you don't need a reference to an individual view.
For example, this image view doesn't have an ID associated with it and
that's okay. Within the Java code of the associated activity or
fragment. If we need a reference to the button, we can simply call findViewById,
which will traverse down the hierarchy until it finds a view with the ID button.
And then it will return that. Similarly, we can traverse down the view
hierarchy to find the linear layout with the ID container, and then return that.
We could do the same to find a reference to this TextView by traversing down
the view hierarchy. But you'll notice that we already have a reference to
the container which is a direct parent of this TextView. Hence, we can just call
container.findViewById to search this subtree to find the TextView with this ID,
and then return it. With this method, we have a smaller sub-tree to search for
a given view, as opposed to searching the entire view hierarchy.
In the Android Java doc for the View class, which is linked below if you want to
follow along, it contains an example where the button with Define in Layout XML.
It was assigned an ID My Button. Then in the Activity, we can use the find
view by ID method, with that ID, so that we can get a reference to the button.
Then we can change it dynamically, such as by adding a click listener to it.
Now in the placeholder fragment class, bind the adapter to the list view.
Luckily, we did assign an ID to the list view earlier. So, we can find it
easily now. Think about the smallest sub-tree in the view hierarchy that you
can call find view by ID on. Then set the adapter on it. If you want an example,
you can see one in the link below. Check the boxes when you're done.